Guide to the Deep Springs College records, 1913-1999.
Deep Springs College records,
- Trustees of Deep Springs (TDS), 1913-1992
  - Trustees of Deep Springs (TDS) Correspondence, 1913-1984
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Income and Expenses November 30, 1967, 1967-11-30 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - DS Correspondence 1968, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - DS Correspondence 1969, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Trustees of Deep Springs Report on Financial Statements; May 31, 1968, 1968-05-31 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence 1970, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence 1971, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence 1972, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence 1973, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence 1974, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence January 3, 1975 -- April 28, 1975, 1975-01-03-1975-04-28 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence May 8, 1975 -- October 22, 1975, 1975-05-08-1975-10-22 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence October 1975, 1975-10 (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
    - Deep Springs College Alaska Natural Gas Pipeline, Undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence May 1, 1976 -- October 28, 1976, 1976-05-01-1976-10-28 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence November 1, 1976 -- May 28, 1977; 1 of 2, 1976-11-01-1977-05-28 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence November 1, 1976 -- May 28, 1977; 2 of 2, 1976-11-01-1977-05-28 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence May 1, 1977 -- October 29, 1977, 1977-05-01-1977-10-29 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence November 6, 1977 -- March 17, 1978, 1977-11-06-1978-03-17 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence March 20, 1978 -- October 31, 1978, 1978-03-20-1978-10-31 (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
    - The Search Committee; Edwin M. Cronk -- Dean and Director, Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Deep Springs College Correspondence November 1, 1978 -- May 2, 1979, 1978-11-01-1979-05-02 (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
    - Deep Springs College Correspondence October 30, 1977 to April 29, 1980, 1977-10-30-1980-04-29 (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
    - Deep Springs Correspondence May 11, 1979 -- October 29, 1979, 1979-05-11-1979-10-29 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Deep Springs College Correspondence May 20, 1980 -- October 31, 1980, 1980-05-20-1980-10-31 (Box 11, Folder 13-14)
    - Deep Springs College Correspondence November 12, 1980 -- May 8, 1981, 1980-11-12-1981-05-08 (Box 11, Folder 15-16)
    - Deep Springs College Correspondence May 15, 1981 -- October 23, 1981, 1981-05-15-1981-10-23 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Deep Springs College Correspondence October 27, 1981 -- May 5, 1982, 1981-10-27-1982-05-05 (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
    - Deep Springs College Correspondence May 9, 1982 -- May 8, 1984, 1982-05-09-1984-05-08 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
    - Ledger, 1923 (Box 12)
- Deep Springs Student Body (DSSB) and alumni materials, 1917-2001
  Access to records more than 50 years old is restricted to the permission of the curator. Access to records less than 50 years old is restricted to the permission of the Student Body.
  - Deep Springs Student Body (DSSB) Minutes, 1917-1997
    - Notes for extracts from minutes 1917-1921, 1917-1921 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Excerpts from the minutes 1917-1945, 1917-1945 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - DSSB Minutes November 1917 -- September 1918, 1917-11-1918-09 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1918 -- June 1919, 1918-09-1919-06 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - DSSB Minutes October 1919 -- June 1920, 1919-10-1920-06 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1920 -- May 1921, 1920-09-1921-05 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1921 -- May 1922, 1921-09-1922-05 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - DSSB Minutes September 122 -- June 1923, 1922-09-1923-06 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1923 -- February 1924, 1923-09-1924-02 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - DSSB Minutes February 1924 -- June 1924, 1924-02-1924-06 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1924 -- May 1925, 1924-09-1925-05 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Faculty Reports 1919-1920, added by Minutes Committee of 1924-1925, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1925 -- June 1926, 1925-09-1926-06 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1926 -- December 1926, 1926-09-1926-12 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1927 -- June 1927, 1927-01-1927-06 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1927 -- June 1928, 1927-09-1928-06 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1928 -- June 1929, 1928-09-1929-06 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1929 -- June 1930, 1929-09-1930-06 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1930 -- May 1931, 1930-09-1931-05 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1931 -- June 1932, 1931-09-1932-06 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1932 -- June 1933, 1932-09-1933-06 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1933 -- June 1934, 1933-09-1934-06 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1934 -- June 1935, 1934-09-1935-06 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1935 -- June 1936, 1935-09-1936-06 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1936 -- June 1937, 1936-09-1937-06 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1937 -- January 1938, 1937-09-1938-01 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1938 -- May 1938, 1938-01-1938-05 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1938 -- December 1938, 1938-09-1938-12 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1939 -- May 1939, 1939-01-1939-05 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1939 -- December 1939, 1939-09-1939-12 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1940 -- May 1940, 1940-01-1940-05 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1940 -- December 1940, 1940-09-1940-12 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1941 -- May 1941, 1941-01-1941-05 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1941 -- December 1941, 1941-09-1941-12 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1942 -- May 1942, 1942-01-1942-05 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1942 -- October 1942, 1942-07-1942-10 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - DSSB Minutes October 1942 -- March 1943, 1942-10-1943-03 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - DSSB Minutes March 1943 -- May 1943, 1943-03-1943-05 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - DSSB Minutes June 1943 -- September 1943, 1943-06-1943-09 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1943 -- December 1943, 1943-09-1943-12 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1944 -- May 1944, 1944-01-1944-05 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1944 -- September 1944, 1944-07-1944-09 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1944 -- December 1944, 1944-09-1944-12 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1945 -- May 1945, 1945-01-1945-05 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1945 -- December 1945, 1945-07-1945-12 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1946 -- May 1946, 1946-01-1946-05 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1946 -- September 1946, 1946-07-1946-09 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - DSSB Minutes October 1946 -- January 1947, 1946-10-1947-01 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1947 -- July 1947, 1947-01-1947-07 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - DSSB Minutes August 1947 -- December 1947, 1947-08-1947-12 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - DSSB Minutes December 1947 -- July 1948, 1947-12-1948-07 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - DSSB Minutes August 1948 -- December 1948, 1948-08-1948-12 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - DSSB Minutes December 1948 -- June 1950, 1948-12-1950-06 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1950 -- May 1951, 1950-09-1951-05 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1951 -- May 1952, 1951-09-1952-05 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1952 -- January 1953, 1952-09-1953-01 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1953 -- May 1953, 1953-01-1953-05 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1953 -- May 1954, 1953-09-1954-05 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - DSSB Minutes October 1954 -- May 1955, 1954-10-1955-05 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1955 -- February 1956, 1955-09-1956-02 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1956 -- May 1956, 1956-01-1956-05 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1956 -- November 1956, 1956-09-1956-11 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - DSSB Minutes November 1956 -- February 1957, 1956-11-1957-02 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - DSSB Minutes February 1957 -- May 1957, 1957-02-1957-05 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1957 -- November 1957, 1957-09-1957-11 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - DSSB Minutes November 1957 -- January 1958, 1957-11-1958-01 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1958 -- May 1958, 1958-01-1958-05 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1958 -- June 1959, 1958-09-1959-06 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1959 -- June 1960, 1959-09-1960-06 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1960 -- May 1961, 1960-09-1961-05 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1961 -- May 1962, 1961-09-1962-05 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1962 -- May 1963, 1962-09-1963-05 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - DSSB Minutes June 1963 -- May 1964, 1963-06-1964-05 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - DSSB Minutes June 1964 -- May 1965, 1964-06-1965-05 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - DSSB Minutes June 1965 -- January 1966, 1965-06-1966-01 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - DSSB Minutes February 1966 -- November 1966, 1966-02-1966-11 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1967 -- January 1968, 1967-01-1968-01 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1968 -- June 1970, 1968-07-1970-06 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - DSSB Minutes June 1970 -- September 1971, 1970-06-1971-09 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1971 -- May 1972, 1971-09-1972-05 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - DSSB Minutes May 1972 -- June 1973, 1972-05-1973-06 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1973 -- June 1974, 1973-07-1974-06 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1974 -- December 1974, 1974-07-1974-12 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1975 -- February 1976, 1975-01-1976-02 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - DSSB Minutes February 1976 -- July 1977, 1976-02-1977-07 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - DSSB Minutes December 1977 -- November 1978, 1977-12-1978-11 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1979 -- June 1979, 1979-01-1979-06 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1979 -- August 1980, 1979-07-1980-08 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1980 -- February 1981, 1980-07-1981-02 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - DSSB Minutes March 1981 -- June 1981, 1981-03-1981-06 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1981 -- November 1981, 1981-07-1981-11 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1982 -- May 1982, 1982-01-1982-05 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - DSSB Minutes June 1982 -- October 1982, 1982-06-1982-10 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - DSSB Minutes October 1982 -- February 1983, 1982-10-1983-02 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - DSSB Minutes February 1983 -- October 1983, 1983-02-1983-10 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - DSSB Minutes October 1983 -- April 1984, 1983-10-1984-04 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - DSSB Minutes April 1984 -- October 1984, 1984-04-1984-10 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - DSSB Minutes November 1984 -- May 1985, 1984-11-1985-05 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - DSSB Minutes June 1985 -- October 1985, 1985-06-1985-10 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - DSSB Minutes October 1985 -- March 1986, 1985-10-1986-03 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - DSSB Minutes October 1986 -- January 1987, 1986-10-1987-01 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - DSSB Minutes March 1987 -- June 1987, 1987-03-1987-06 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1987 -- February 1988, 1987-07-1988-02 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - DSSB Minutes 1987 -- 1988 Original Drafts and Miscellany, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - DSSB Minutes March 1988 -- July 1988, 1988-03-1988-07 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - DSSB Minutes August 1988 -- November 1988, 1988-08-1988-11 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1989 -- June 1989, 1989-01-1989-06 (Box 15, Folder 20-22)
    - DSSB Minutes June 1989 -- August 1989, 1989-06-1989-08 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - DSSB Minutes August 1989 -- September 1989, 1989-08-1989-09 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - DSSB Minutes October 1989 -- November 1989, 1989-10-1989-11 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1990 -- February 1990, 1990-01-1990-02 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - DSSB Minutes March 1990 -- June 1990, 1990-03-1990-06 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - DSSB minutes May 1990 -- June 1990, 1990-05-1990-06 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - DSSB Minutes May 1990 -- June 1990 (original notes), 1990-05-1990-06 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1990 -- October 1990, 1990-07-1990-10 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1991 -- February 1991, 1991-01-1991-02 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - DSSB Minutes March 1991 -- April 1991, 1991-03-1991-04 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - DSSB Minutes May 1991 -- June 1991, 1991-05-1991-06 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1991 -- August 1991, 1991-07-1991-08 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - DSSB Minutes August 1991 -- October 1991, 1991-08-1991-10 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1992 -- February 1992, 1992-01-1992-02 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - DSSB Minutes March 1992 -- April 1992, 1992-03-1992-04 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - DSSB Minutes May 1992 -- June 1992, 1992-05-1992-06 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1992 -- August 1992, 1992-07-1992-08 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - DSSB Minutes August 1992 -- October 1992, 1992-08-1992-10 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - DSSB Minutes October 1992 -- February 1993, 1992-10-1993-02 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - DSSB Minutes May 1993 -- June 1993, 1993-05-1993-06 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1993 -- August 1993, 1993-07-1993-08 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - DSSB Minutes August 1993 -- October 1993, 1993-08-1993-10 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - DSSB Minutes October 1993 -- November 1993, 1993-10-1993-11 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1994 -- February 1994, 1994-01-1994-02 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - DSSB Minutes February 1993 -- April 1994, 1993-02-1994-04 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - DSSB Minutes May 1994 -- June 1994, 1994-05-1994-06 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - DSSB Minutes July 1994 -- Augut 1994, 1994-07-1994-08 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1994 -- November 1994, 1994-09-1994-11 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - DSSB Minutes January 1995 -- February 1995, 1995-01-1995-02 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - DSSB Minutes March 1995 -- April 1995, 1995-03-1995-04 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - DSSB Minutes May 1995 -- June 1995, 1995-05-1995-06 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - DSSB Minutes June 1995 -- March 1996, 1995-06-1996-03 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - DSSB Minutes September 1996 -- April 1997 and Miscellany, 1996-09-1997-04 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Correspondence, Memoirs, Etc., 1924-1986
    - Letters from Alumni for General Consumption 1951-1983, 1951-1983 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Legends of Deep Springs 1983-1986, 1983-1986 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - 1964 Alumni Solicited Essays, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Riley Kent Davis 1970, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Chet Dunn c. 1974, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Lawrence Kimpton 1951-1977, 1951-1977 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Fred Laise, Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Frank Lerrigo 1982 letter and copy of a 1924 Diary of Death Valley SB Trip, 1924-1982 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Frank Noon, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - P.N. Nunn Writings and Appreciation 1922-1930, 1922-1930 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Vern Penner, Farewell Address 1960, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Randall Reid 1973-1976, 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Herb Reich 1993, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Martin Sachse 1924, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - David and Sharon Schuman 1982, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Robert Sproull 1974, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Julian Steward 1977, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Francis Tetrault 1985, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Walter Welti 1974, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Sid Walcott 1977, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - H.R. Waldo on Deep Springs 1973-1977, 1973-1977 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Withrow to Mansfield 1940 First Fundraising Pitch, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Essays and Miscellany, Undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - The Harlequin, Beaver, Utah; 1915-1916 -- 1 black notebook (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Student, Community, Committee, and Class Projects, 1920-1999
    - Deep Springs Students Creative Writing, Undated (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
    - Telluride Association and Deep Springs Work, ca. 1932, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Cultural Presentations, Undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - 1924 Telluride Association Insert, Deep Springs Co-operation, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - 1920 Census of Deep Springs, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - "Whympin" by Park Honan, June 1948, 1948-06 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - PlanCom 1967, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Report of the DSSB Survey Committee to TDS 1951, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - DSSB Alumni Questionnaires 1946-1964, 1946-1964 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Report on the Committee on the Ground Rules and Correspondence 1981, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - The Social Organization of Deep Springs 1965, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - E. Root Essay from Nunn Library, Undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Telluride Topics, Undated (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Deep Springs College Records and Archives 1973-1974, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - "The Jewish Quota at Deep Springs" Harvey Mansfield 1944, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Special Report by the Student Body Representative, Eric Swanson 1967 re: Drug Use, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Early History of Deep Springs, Undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - The Four Quarter Proposal, Roger Dell c. 1963, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Planning 1966-1968, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Deep Springs newsletters and brochures, 1966-1999
    - Deep Springs Newsletters, Fall 1987 -- Fall 1999, 1987-1999 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Deep Springs Newsletters, February 1966 -- Summer 1987, 1966-02-1987 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Deep Springs Brochures, Undated (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  - Deep Springs and Nunn Press Coverage (1958-1999), 1990-1991
    - Miscellaneous Materials on Nunn Compiled by Brad Edmondson; 1991, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - "Former Head of Honors Program Falsely Claimed to Have Doctorate, Report Says"; Great Falls Tribune; c. 1990, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Nunn and Related Correspondence, Undated
    - Nunn Letters, Undated (Box 17, Folder 42-43)
  - Histories of Deep Springs, Undated
    - Deep Springs: Years of Transition, by Robert B. Aird -- 1 unbound volume, Undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - A History of Deep Springs: General Chronicle 1900-1930 by Ernes S. Tucker III, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - A History of Deep Springs: General Chronicle 1930-1950 by William Waina, Undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - A History of Deep Springs: The Early Educational Enterprises of Mr. L.L. Nunn by Humphrey J. Fisher, Undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - A History of Deep Springs: The Founding of Deep Springs by I. Stephen Rabin, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - A History of Deep Springs: The Relations of L.L. Nunn to Deep Springs by Bruce Barkley, Undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - A History of Deep Springs: The Relations of the Directors and Deans to Deep Springs by Don O. Noel Jr., Undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - A History of Deep Springs: History of the Curriculum by Miles C. Everett, Undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - A History of Deep Springs: History of the Student Body 1917-1932 by James L. Barkenquast, Undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - A History of Deep Springs: A History of the Student Body (Part Two) 1932-1951 by Arden Smith, Undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - A History of Deep Springs: History of the Work Program by Charles Steensma, Undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - A History of Deep Springs: An Account of Student Trips by George Robinson, Undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - A History of Deep Springs: The Tellurdie Association and Deep Springs by Roger Pierce, Undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - A History of Deep Springs: A History of the Financial Troubles of the Institution by Noel Burleson, Undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Photographs and images
  - "Photographs" - 1 large bound album of unidentified plans and diagrams (Box 19)
  - "Photographs" - 2 large bound albums of unidentified plans and diagrams (Box 20)
  - "Photographs" - 1 large bound album of unidentified plans and diagrams (Box 21)
  - Telluride Image Index, "Telluride Power," 3 CDs of TPC, TA, and DS images, digital versions of TA History Projects (Sweeting MSS., Bailey's Memoir, ADSTA Oral History Project, etc.) (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Deep Springs Archive photos, CD-3983 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - DEC Nunn Archive Images Vol. 2, CD-3984 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    CD Vol 1 DEC Nunn Archive images empty case